英文字幕:
官方
翻译: 谷歌翻译
校对 润色 压制:
Bolshevik0
Hello everyone, my name is Kirill Yudintsev, I am the Creative Director of Gaijin Entertainment.
大家好 我是Kirill Yudintsev 我是Gaijin娱乐公司的创意总监
Today I'll be answering a number of your questions.
今天我会回答你们的一些问题
A hot question.
一个热门的问题
A lot of people are asking about the P-47 and its performance in Random battles,
很多人都在问随机战斗中的P-47以及它的性能问题
they ask if we are going to do something or change something about it.
他们问我们是否要做什么或者改什么
First of all, we've just adjusted its BR, it will be a bit higher now.
首先 我们调高了它的权重
Then we'll work with the statistics, will see why and how it affects the outcomes in Random Battles, and then
然后 我们将根据统计数据 了解它对随机战斗结果的影响
depending on what we see, we might introduce further changes in the nearest future.
然后 根据这些结果 再进行进一步的改变
Thank you for writing about things that concern you.
谢谢你写下你所关心的问题
It's very important for us as it allows us to improve the game.
这对我们非常重要 因为它可以让我们改进游戏
Many players ask about new game modes.
许多玩家询问新的游戏模式
We actually organize a lot of different events with different rules
我们实际上组织了许多不同玩法的活动
that deviate from what you see in Random Battles.
这些不同于随机战斗
The thing is that it's rather difficult to introduce new game modes in Random Battles,
事实上在随机战斗中引入新的游戏模式相当困难
because we want them to be fair and balanced.
因为我们希望新模式足够公平和平衡
This makes it quite challenging. Everything should be balanced.
这件事做起来不那么容易 颇具挑战性 其中的一切都应该平衡
If we want the changes to be balanced,
如果我们希望这些变化是平衡的
to make fair game modes, especially the asymmetric ones
制定公平的游戏模式 尤其是不对称的游戏模式
that a lot of players want if we want it to be engaging and fair,
正如许多玩家所想的那样 如果我们让它变得有趣又公平
it's much much more difficult than to make a separate event
要比做出一个独立的活动困难很多
that inherently has limitations like what kind of vehicles are allowed, how many players are in etc.
从对战本质上就限制了很多 譬如允许使用哪些载具 有多少玩家等等
That's why, first of all, do participate in our events! Right now it's Chronicles, for example.
所以的话 请先参加我们组织的活动 譬如现在的二战编年史
There are a lot of interesting mechanics out there for you to try.
活动中有很多有趣的机制让你去尝试
Apart from that, we are currently testing World War.
除此之外 我们正在测试世界大战模式
This gamemode has a lot of new mechanics such as convoy and escort missions.
这个游戏模式有很多新的机制 譬如护航和护航任务
These are missions of a completely new type, they are asymmetric, it's all very engaging and historical.
这些全新类型的任务 既不对称又非常具有吸引力和历史性
Well, it's much closer to what most real combat missions were,
它更接近大多数真实战斗任务
than the balanced skirmishes of two even sides.
而不是双方均衡的小规模冲突
These feel more like combat scenarios.
这些感觉更像是战场
That's why I strongly suggest that you should try it.
这就是我强烈建议你尝试它的原因
Sign up for it, leave your feedback.
注册并留下你的反馈
We never test new game modes and new mechanics in Random Battles, we don't want to break it.
我们不想打破以往的规矩 就是不在随机战斗中测试新的游戏模式和新机制
We do it in our events or during tournaments
而是在活动和竞技场中进行测试
or, like now, in World War which is a completely new level altogether.
或者像现在这样 完全在一个新的模式世界大战中
Leave your feedback, maybe some of these mechanics will make it to Random Battles as well. We will see.
留下你的反馈意见 也许一些新机制会出现在随机战斗中
Many people ask about Italian armour, a lot of players already own Italian premiums and aircraft.
很多人在问意大利陆战的事情 很多玩家已经拥有意大利的金币载具和飞机
There are already Italian tanks in-game, two premium machines.
游戏中已经有两辆意大利金币载具
A huge thanks to all who buy them, support our game and leave their feedback.
非常感谢所有购买它们来支持我们的游戏并反馈意见的人
We're already working on a full size ground tech tree for Italy.
我们已经在做意大利的完整陆战科技树
We'll do our best to release it this year.
我们尽量在年内发布它
Maybe some tanks will appear in the game even earlier than that.
有些坦克也许会比这更早地出现
Creating the Italian ground tech tree is a very challenging process.
创建意大利陆战科技树是一个非常具有挑战性的过程
吐槽:
官方玩梗最为致命
We do love pizza and pasta, but it doesn't make it easier to find data on all those vehicles.
我们确实喜欢披萨和意大利面 但这并不利于查找所有这些陆战载具的数据
Many players are concerned about the role the M1 Abrams has in Random Battles,
许多玩家都关心M1艾布拉姆斯在随机战斗中的角色
where it performs pretty well, mostly thanks to its excellent survivability.
它的表现相当不错 主要归功于其卓越的生存能力
We've only implemented the feature the Abrams has in real life
我们只实现了Abrams在现实中的特点
that it has a chance of surviving a fire in the ammunition storage.
也就是有可能在弹药舱起火的状态下幸免于难
In our game it works even better than in real life though,
尽管如此 它在我们的游戏中的表现要比现实中的更好
because in reality there was always a chance that the engine transmission compartment would catch fire as well
因为实际上发动机和传动系统总是有可能一起着火
and to prevent that you had to rotate the turret.
为了防止动力舱一起着火 你得转动炮塔
It's a fairly lengthy process, during which the tank is obviously unable to fight.
这是一个相当漫长的过程 在这个过程中坦克显然无法战斗
In the end the fire disables the vehicle anyway, and the crew, as a general rule, abandons it.
最后 火灾总是会使车辆无法使用 并且成员通常会放弃它
We plan to make it as realistic as possible.
我们计划让这些尽可能还原
If your ammo rack is on fire, you'll have to turn your turret away from the engine transmission compartment.
如果你的弹药架着火 则你必须将炮塔从动力舱上方移开
That's the first thing.
这是第一件事
The second is that right now the piece of armour that separates the rack and the fighting compartment is way too sturdy,
第二件事则是 现在把弹药架和战斗室隔开的那部分装甲太坚固了
making the tank practically invincible to the attacks from the rear.
使坦克几乎可以无视来自炮塔后方的攻击
It's not the way it works in real life, so we'll be working on that as well.
现实中并非如此 所以这点以后也会被改进
Perhaps, if your rack catches fire, we'll make it impossible for a reload to finish. We'll see.
如果你的弹药架着火了 也许就不能再装填弹药 我们拭目以待
Maybe that will be enough.
也许这些改进就足够了
Because right now it's way tougher than in real life, and tougher than its opponents in the game.
因为现在这样要比现实中的更强 也比它的对手更强
After we introduced new top tanks for a number of countries in the latest patch,
在最新版本中为多个国家推出新的顶级坦克之后
many of you started to question the competitiveness of Japan, France and Germany at high ranks.
你们中的许多人开始质疑日本 法国和德国的顶级房水准
In one of the upcoming big updates we plan to introduce new vehicles for France.
在即将到来的重大更新之一中 我们计划为法国推出新的陆战载具
Japan is in for a treat as well.
同样还有日本
Maybe Germans will get a production Leopard 2.
也许德系会得到一个豹2系列的坦克
So they will get more powerful vehicles as well.
所以他们也会获得更为强大的车辆
By the way, the info about these plans was already shown on our website.
顺便说一句 在我们的网站上能找到关于这些计划的信息
As well as a lot of other exciting pieces of information.
以及许多其他令人兴奋的信息
Check out the news on our website right now!
请马上看看我们网站上的新闻吧
As a kind of a follow-up to the last Q&A session,
作为上次问答部分的后续
a lot of players write that the 6th rank and top-tier aircraft aren't that difficult to implement.
很多玩家都说 6级和顶级飞机并不难实现
That the early self-guided and guided missiles weren't that effective and won't change the flow of a match,
早期的被动制导和主动制导导弹没有那么有效 也不会改变游戏的流程
that it's a kind of a nice thing to have that doesn't change everything,
没多大变化是好事
doesn't make WT in a new game that is completely different.
这不会让战争雷霆变得完全不同
And all of that makes sense but you have to understand that if we introduce just the F-100 and the MiG-19
这些说的都有道理 但是你必须理解如果我们只推出F-100和米格-19
吐槽:
我闻到了一股批判DCS的味道
it will make WT into a game about duels.
就会让战争雷霆成为一场关于决斗的游戏
And our game is very different from that after all.
毕竟我们的游戏与此截然不同
There are more than two nations, we have bombers and other types of aircraft.
我们有两个以上的国家 以及轰炸机和其他类型的飞机
That might look fairly easy. And it actually is, to implement two aircraft that can fight each other on even terms.
要实现两架可以相互对抗的飞机可能挺简单的
But we need to make it interesting for all countries,
但是我们需要加入所有国家的飞机
to make it balanced, to make it possible for bombers to play with them.
让整场游戏变得平衡 同时轰炸机也可以加入战斗
Because guided missiles or heat seekers weren't that effective against fighter aircraft,
由于制导导弹或红外导引头对战斗机不是很有效
but were much more effective against bomber aircraft.
但是对轰炸机来说效率要高得多
This might even out the field with top-tier bombers, but it will change the game in a lot of ways nevertheless.
这甚至超出了顶级轰炸机的领域 但是不管怎样 这会大幅改变游戏
All in all, WT isn't just about two aircraft, isn't just about duels.
总而言之 战争雷霆不是关于两架飞机决斗的游戏
That's why it's a lot of work, and we want it to be, as much as possible.
这就是为啥6级飞机的实现仍然比较困难 而且我们也想实现很多机制
A whole new level for both aviation and gameplay,
对于空战和游戏玩法来说都是全新的层次
not just an attention grabber in the form of two supersonic jets and their missiles.
不仅仅是吸引热度的两个超音速喷气式飞机和它们的导弹
That's why that requires a bit more in terms of our effort, with a lot of tests and brainstorming involved.
这就是我们需要更加努力的原因 这需要进行大量的测试和头脑风暴
Thanks for watching this episode of our developer Q&A,
感谢观看我们这集开发者问答
thanks for watching the previous one and writing your questions.
同时感谢你们在看完前面那期之后的留言
Leave questions and feedback, we read it all, it's all very educational and exciting.
在油管的评论区留下问题和反馈 我们都会看一遍 这都是非常有教育意义和令人兴奋的
Leave likes and subscribe to the channel!
到油管上点赞并订阅本频道